<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ccie on RichardStrnad.ch</title>
    <link>https://www.richardstrnad.ch/tags/ccie/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ccie on RichardStrnad.ch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 07:00:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.richardstrnad.ch/tags/ccie/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year &amp; Resolutions for 2017</title>
      <link>https://www.richardstrnad.ch/2017/01/01/happy-new-year-resolutions-for-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 07:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.richardstrnad.ch/2017/01/01/happy-new-year-resolutions-for-2017/</guid>
      <description>2016 is over, at least here in switzerland. It was an interesting year for me, i attend my first Cisco Live (@Vegas) and had to recertify my CCIE for the first time. As the new year starts i&amp;rsquo;m taking a new challenge @Netcloud as Network Engineer. I have different things that i want to accomplish in 2017.
   Title Description     Run on 200 days About 4 Days a week, this will be hard but should be doable   First Marathon Already booked, Berlin in September   Read 26 Books I will create a list and keep track of this on a separate post   Improve my Spanish I learned some basic Spanish skills last year and put them in use on my trip to central america, but i definitely want improve   Get my CCIE Datacenter I&amp;rsquo;m already working on this   Blog Redesign An easy one, but it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new look    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benefits of becoming a CCIE</title>
      <link>https://www.richardstrnad.ch/2014/05/07/benefits-of-becoming-a-ccie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2014 17:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.richardstrnad.ch/2014/05/07/benefits-of-becoming-a-ccie/</guid>
      <description>Beside of your number and that you&amp;rsquo;re recognised as CCIE you also get some small perks from Cisco:
CCIE Certification Kit
You will get a CCIE Certification Kit, after i got mine i will blog about it for sure!
According to cisco it includes:
  Congratulatory letter from John Chambers Certificate of achievement Personalized CCIE plaque CCIE badge pull CCIE sticker set Certification resource document   I will post the whole package and its content after i received my Certification Kit</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
